<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Shows on The Waters Above</title><link>https://www.thewatersabove.org/shows/</link><description>Recent content in Shows on The Waters Above</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 16:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.thewatersabove.org/shows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rage Against the State</title><link>https://www.thewatersabove.org/shows/rage-against-the-state/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 16:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.thewatersabove.org/shows/rage-against-the-state/</guid><description>Rage Against the State is a freedom-themed festival in Bozeman, MT organized by Roger Roots, nationally recognized attorney and prominent Montana libertarian.
The event will include literature, music, comedy, and lectures. If you lean towards libertarianism, anarcho-capitalism, or your friends call you a &amp;ldquo;conspiracy theorist,&amp;rdquo; you will be right at home.
We&amp;rsquo;ll be playing in the afternoon/evening.
Exact location is currently being determined.
This page will soon be updated with the exact venue and time.</description></item><item><title>The Rabbit Hole</title><link>https://www.thewatersabove.org/shows/the-rabbit-hole/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 21:00:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.thewatersabove.org/shows/the-rabbit-hole/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ll be playing a live solo concert for The Rabbit Hole, is a salon for open-minded individuals in Sandpoint, Idaho. These folks were some of the first people that I connected with after waking up. Incredibly warm, welcoming, bright, and open. You would do well to establish a community as healthy as this one.
&amp;ndash; David</description></item><item><title>Friends of Montana</title><link>https://www.thewatersabove.org/shows/friends-of-montana/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 19:00:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.thewatersabove.org/shows/friends-of-montana/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ll be playing an online solo concert for the Friends of Montana, a tight-knit group of concerned citizens in the State of Montana. Constantly discussing new information, inquisitive minds like these are critical to turning the tide. I feel honored to perform for them.
&amp;ndash; David</description></item></channel></rss>